[{"answer": "Well, she's in a different prison in reality.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Before we get to that, how would you categorize where she is now?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, she's -- she accepts her reality.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "How does she deal with that, do you think?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think anybody killed her.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Have you formed any kind of opinion about that?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, she's a young woman, just slightly older than some of my grandchildren.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What kind of woman is she?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Judges, clerks, deputies, witnesses, lawyers, jurors.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "They perform, didn't they?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, I guess anything is possible.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Could she be pulling the wool over your eyes?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, she will read books.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "What will she be doing tomorrow for example?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "She probably would.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "You think she'd like to be a mother again?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I found the testimony incredibly moving.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Lisa, what did you make of it today?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "It would be if he were the sole witness or if he were the victim.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Is it significant that his story is slightly changing?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "In your experience in this field, it can't be uncommon that a 14-year-old boy would perhaps have memory issues with this kind of thing, could it?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I think Doty's importance is clear.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What is their importance in this now?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, it's a tragedy because it shows what happens when you have an icon and when football becomes too important at a university.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "In relation to Joe Paterno?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Actually both were.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "You mean \"Dallas,\" not the royal wedding?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "More.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Was it all you hoped it would be when you signed up for this?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "We had this realization we would never work together again.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Really, why?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I mean, you look so nice and normal today.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Were you remotely concerned, given that you were the top dog, if you like, that it might damage the brand?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "About until they told me how much I was going to make.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "How long did you think about it?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "How much was it?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't be doing it without them.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "How much did the friendship come into it?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "So far, yeah.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Is everything OK, back to normal?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "In Germany, it's not my chuckle.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Was that your chuckle or was it one you perfected?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "He said that.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Did you really say that?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "No wonder I drank.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "You think that's evil?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I don't think I was an evil man.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Did you like being, for what you were for a long time, the most evil man on television?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Especially against his own family.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "That is evil, isn't it?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Of course I do, yes.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Did you like the reputation?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "They -- the question they say is who shot J.R.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "How do people react even now?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Yes, yeah.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "You ever tell them?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Bing Crosby's daughter.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Everywhere.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "When you guys are filming in Dallas, presuming you live there for the duration, when you walk around, it must be like the royal family, isn't it?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "I think it was in the U.K.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Where are you most popular outside America?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Every night, yeah.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Well, I actually was completely excited about what I considered to be a fun challenge.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "John Ross was a little baby.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Is he everything like his father or nothing like his father?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "It's been wonderful.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "How have you found it coming into this iconic show?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "I was born in 1980.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "How old were you when \"Dallas\" -- how old are you, if you don't mind me asking?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "You know, I feel incredibly blessed to have the opportunity to be another television phenomenon.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Jesse, for you, from \"Desperate House Wives\" to \"Dallas,\" does it get any better?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "They're going to drag us into another 13 years.", "docId": "120612pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Can we have a little critique?", "qSentId": 698}]